{
  "title": "Sample Game",
  "author": "Brandon Ingli",
  "description": "A Sample Game for the Question and Answer game engine.",
  "categories": [
    {
      "category": "Tutorial",
      "clues": [
        {
          "points": 200,
          "answer": "Click anywhere on the clue to reveal the question.",
          "question": "What is \"You did it\"?"
        },
        {
          "points": 400,
          "answer": "This is how you add and remove teams.",
          "question": "What is by clicking Add/Remove in the lower left?"
        },
        {
          "points": 650,
          "answer": "This is how you change scores and team names.",
          "question": "What are by clicking on the name or score, or pressing the +/- buttons?"
        },
        {
          "points": 500,
          "answer": "If you click the X icon instead of the clue, this happens.",
          "question": "What is the clue remains visible on the board and the last score counter remains the same?"
        },
        {
          "points": 1000,
          "answer": "True or False: Game Progress and Scores save if you refresh.",
          "question": "What is False?"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "One Clue",
      "clues": [
        {
          "points": 400,
          "dailyDouble": true,
          "answer": "This is the only clue in the category.",
          "question": "What is cool?"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Six Clues",
      "clues": [
        {
          "points": 1,
          "answer": "Clue number one.",
          "question": "What is question number one?"
        },
        {
          "points": 2,
          "answer": "Clue number two.",
          "question": "What is question number two?"
        },
        {
          "points": 3,
          "answer": "Clue number three.",
          "question": "What is question number three?"
        },
        {
          "points": 4,
          "answer": "Clue number four.",
          "question": "What is question number four?"
        },
        {
          "points": 5,
          "answer": "Clue number five.",
          "question": "What is question number five?"
        },
        {
          "points": 6,
          "answer": "Clue number six.",
          "question": "What is question number six?"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Five More Clues",
      "clues": [
        {
          "points": 1,
          "answer": "Clue number one.",
          "question": "What is question number one?"
        },
        {
          "points": 2,
          "answer": "Clue number two.",
          "question": "What is question number two?"
        },
        {
          "points": 3,
          "answer": "Clue number three.",
          "question": "What is question number three?"
        },
        {
          "points": 4,
          "answer": "Clue number four.",
          "question": "What is question number four?"
        },
        {
          "points": 5,
          "answer": "Clue number five.",
          "question": "What is question number five?"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "This category name is quite long for an Answer and Question",
      "clues": [
        {
          "points": 1,
          "answer": "Clue number one.",
          "question": "What is question number one?"
        },
        {
          "points": 2,
          "answer": "Clue number two.",
          "question": "What is question number two?"
        },
        {
          "points": 3,
          "answer": "Clue number three.",
          "question": "What is question number three?"
        },
        {
          "points": 4,
          "answer": "Clue number four.",
          "question": "What is question number four?"
        },
        {
          "points": 5,
          "answer": "Clue number five.",
          "question": "What is question number five?"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "A long name for a category",
      "clues": [
        {
          "points": 1,
          "answer": "Clue number one.",
          "question": "What is question number one?"
        },
        {
          "points": 2,
          "answer": "Clue number two.",
          "question": "What is question number two?"
        },
        {
          "points": 3,
          "answer": "Clue number three.",
          "question": "What is question number three?"
        },
        {
          "points": 4,
          "answer": "Clue number four.",
          "question": "What is question number four?"
        },
        {
          "points": 5,
          "answer": "Clue number five.",
          "question": "What is question number five?"
        }
      ]
    }
    
  ]
}